Domain expansion.
Chimera's Shadow Garden.
Esoteric technique.
Hollow Wicker Basket.
Hollow Wicker Basket is the origin
of new Shadow Style's simple domain.
It possesses the ability to neutralize a
domain and counter its
guaranteed hit factor.
This won't end well for you.
The domain amplification
used by Drogo and Hanami
in Shibuya used a domain
capable of guaranteed hit,
guaranteed kill technique.
How is he able to hit me?
But they intentionally left a
space in their curse technique?
So that Gojo's curse
technique could flow into it.
Neutralizing is limitless. However,
Hollow Wicker Basket
and Simple Domain aren't
capable of neutralizing the
curse technique. So instead,
they work by neutralizing the barrier
that's imbued with curse technique.
In this way, the imbued technique's
guaranteed hit effect is nullified.
But Fushiguro's domain is incomplete.
Guess that wiped the sneer off your face.
You damn brat!
When he transposed his domain
onto the space of the gymnasium,
an unexpected consequence happened.
It forced his domain to close.
It is not imbued with a
guaranteed hit technique.
You're acting like you've already won!
Now I get it.
Chimera Shadow Garden.
It is currently extending Fushiguro's
Ten Shadows technique, and as it does so,
draws out 120 % of his latent potential.
Unfortunately for Registar, that very
imperfection is what caught him off guard.
Both his clones and his Shikigami had
physical forms before striking me.
That means this build isn't imbued
with a guaranteed hit technique.
The domain's buff to his technique's
abilities is no joke, though.
This is even worse to deal with
than a simple guaranteed hit domain.
If he pulls that elephant out
here and drenches me in water,
it'll take away half of my
options, and I'll probably lose!
But, you know, it's so like me
to make sure that won't happen.
Too slow.
I have it figured out.
Yes, I knew it.
I've had to reinforce my footing with
cursed energy to avoid getting sucked in.
Because the whole bottom of this
domain is your shadow, right?
You're able to remove and
store objects and yourself.
That's pretty convenient.
But one thing kept nagging at me.
Why doesn't this guy have
more weapons he can use?
You just use that one paltry
curse tool over and over.
Maybe it's a low-capacity tool and
you're trying to reserve as much
space for yourself just in case
you need it for something later on.
Either that,
or you're being forced
to bear the weight of
the objects that are
stored in your shadow.
Sounds like the latter was spot-hard.
Now I've turned the design
of your domain against you.
With three passenger cars, your current
weight is approximately 2.4 tons.
Looks like your clones
weren't able to tolerate it,
And I bet you can't even
produce your Shikigami now.
Either way, I'll just need to keep
minding my footing around you.
As I keep adding weight until
you're crushed under it.
Are you stupid or something?
Even if it's incomplete, a
domain is still a domain!
My shadow is everywhere!
Which one of us will get crushed first?
Horanji!
I'm wondering why this
with force T pergi Thenhome
I'm feeling
T Love me Love me Willbble
It is said that a typical human will
lose consciousness at 5 to 6 Gs,
2.4 tons. tons.
Because Fushiguro weighed
only 60 kilograms,
that meant he was currently
suffering the equivalent of 40 G's.
In order to prevent his blood
from pooling in his legs
from the high G's and depriving
his brain of blood flow,
Fushiguro was lowering his posture and
reinforcing his body with cursed energy,
paying special attention to his legs.
A mature African elephant
weighs three to six tons.
With the domain's improvement
to his technique's accuracy,
Mac's elephant accurately
recreated its real weight.
Under that weight, Registar's right
fibula and heel bone were cracking.
Both of them were now under
enormous strain and faced
the possibility of being
crushed to death at any second.
I screwed up.
I could have won if I had
kept the trucks in reserve.
What do I do?
I got splashed with some water at the
same time but my trump card's still safe.
I could slip into his shadow and
recreate my trump card inside it.
That would crush him for sure.
No.
He's not dismissing his domain.
But when he does decide to
dismiss it, it means anything.
I'm still in his shadow is
going to be stuck inside there!
What if I'm stuck in his shadow forever?
I'll be there even after he dies!
What's it like inside his shadow anyway?
It looks like a liquid.
But what if I can't breathe in it?
Can I float? Keep fighting!
Submerging into his shadow is too risky!
I'm out of time!
Super Wild's stuck in this state!
I have to pull out my
trump card and activate it!
CONTRACTUAL RECREATION!
I didn't make it in time.
And now I know there's no
oxygen inside of his shadow.
No.
No buoyancy.
No resistance, either.
I'm just...
sinking.
My consciousness...
is... fading.
Not yet.
Keep enduring it.
I'll wait until I'm sure he's
dead, before dismissing the Domain.
Then I can expel whatever's in my shadow!
The things I recreate,
they disappear soon after carrying out
whatever command I gave them to carry out.
However, I didn't give those
cars I sank any command.
After all, I didn't want
them disappearing on me.
That means I could still issue
them a command if I want.
Something like, take me and rise up.
The weight of one car is gone now, but
it was totally worth it to save my life.
Tell you what!
I am man enough to admit it!
You are strong.
But not as strong as me!
Contractual recreation!
A 132-square-foot, two-story
wooden frame structure!
The framework alone
weighs at least 30 tons!
And I'm commanding it to crush you!
What happened did I fall
back into his shadow again?
No I'm in actual water.
How it's heavy what's that
Brett trying to do strangle me?
What power?
No that's wrong.
This is from the weight of
those two cars that I added.
This is bad.
This time, I'm really sinking.
I have to dismiss contractual recreation.
Oh, right.
The community gymnasium.
And in the gym's basement
is a heated swimming pool.
Did he go hiding in a shadow
and dismiss his domain?
That could have forced me to destroy
the floor and plunge into the pool.
You can't use your receipts
when they're that wet, can you?
He waited instead of pursuing me right
away does that mean his technique
still needs to recover after his domain
exhausted it that's what you think
are you sure i'm sure that you
can't produce your shikigami in your
current condition yeah that's true so
you do understand And what comes next,
don't you?
He's going to use a
Shikigami, just not that dog.
But none of his other ones
can deal a decisive blow.
Fine, use it.
The moment that you let up on me,
I'll finish you with a counterattack.
Let's go.
You thought demon dog
was some weak shikigami?
You were wrong.
What did I tell you before?
These sorcerers are all liars.
The domain, the pool, all to convince
me you couldn't use that dog anymore.
You didn't escape into this
gymnasium, you lured me into it.
To think I'd let a modern sorcerer and
a braddock bat get the better of me.
Nui can't fly that far carrying
me, so I couldn't escape.
I've had trouble with that before.
Tell me, how are you connected to Tengen?
Who are you talking about?
Oh, right, Tengen.
That hermit would still be alive.
Must be history's greatest shut-in.
Okay, that's enough.
Reggie said Tengen's claims about
the calling game were a bluff.
I'd be smart to consider the possibility
Tengen and Kenjaku are secretly connected.
And that they're both
lying about their endgames.
But that doesn't seem likely
from Reggie's reaction.
Kogane
Transfer all my points
over to this little brat.
Okay.
Congratulations, you have been
granted 41 points by Registar.
And in return...
Must you assume I have some evil plot?
I want to do at least one
good deed before I die.
By the way, I'm just a spectator here.
Kenjaku and I weren't ever close friends.
But I do like this game.
It certainly makes things interesting.
That's my intuition anyway.
Wait.
Now do me a favor.
After all, you did kill me.
The favor is, let fate toy with
you before you die like a fool.
You have gained five points for a kill.
I got him.
Nope, because you dropped your guard.
You think you're Mr.
Tough Guy?
What the hell?
Why is your whole body covered in lotion?
It might actually be Sauce.
Just die!
I pray it's only Sauce.
Seriously, what's with this guy?
I've blown him up a lot!
I feel like I've killed
him at least five times.
So how come he has so little damage?
What's wrong with Sauce?
Even his giant head wound has healed up.
But he hasn't shown any signs of using
reverse curse techniques like I do.
I don't get what's going on with him.
Player Hazenoki.
What do you want?
I regret to inform you that Player
Registar has just died. Huh?
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going home.
I'm sick of this.
Oh, well, take a bath
and brush your teeth.
Hey!
How about giving me your points?
Don't follow me.
Oh, come on!
Just think of it as paying it forward.
Just die.
Takaba's curse technique, Comedian,
takes whatever he's convinced would
be funny and turns it into a reality.
Even Satoru Gojo is incapable
of opposing this technique.
Yet Takaba is utterly clueless
as to how his technique works.
I don't get it. I don't get it!
Ever since I became an adult,
I hardly understand anything!
I've heard that all men
are actually wolves.
But it's always those wolves who take
care of the confusing stuff for me!
It's a win-win situation!
The wolves love being in charge, and
I love not thinking about anything.
Men always want to do stuff
for me because I'm so cute.
The wolves will always...
always...
Megumi, don't.
You're not killing me?
Damn it, sis.
Shut up already.
Events progressed quickly in the Sendai
colony, far outstripping those of Tokyo.
They also started to
become increasingly fierce.
Drew Vlactawala.
Current points, 91.
This is his second incarnation.
He's an old man who
single-handedly conquered
this archipelago during
the Civil War of Wa.
He possesses two autonomous Shikigami,
and the orbit of those
Shikigami determines his domain.
Ryu Ishigori.
Current points, 77.
He has the greatest
cursed energy firepower
among any other remaining
player in the game.
Takako Uro.
Current points, 70.
She was originally the captain of
the Sun, Moon, and Stars squad,
assassins for the Fujiwara clan.
Her technique can manipulate the sky.
Kurourushi.
Current points, 54.
A cockroach-cursed spirit that
Kenjaku freed from the control
of cursed spirit manipulation.
It ranks as a previously
registered special grade.
It's
currently lying dormant until
certain conditions are met.
There was no alliance between them,
but their complex
compatibility and opposing
strength led them into
a four-way stalemate.
But one of those pillars has fallen.
Yuta Okotsu.
Current points, 35.
Three months after the
night parade of 100 demons,
he blossomed as a special-grade sorcerer.
He is a modern sorcerer rivaling
the abilities of even Satoru Gojo.
The end of the day.
The day of the day.
There is no one thing.
It's not one thing.
It's almost like.
It's like.
You
Let's get started.
I'll obtain 400 points on my own.
Which would you like, Yuta?
It's called Gurawarushi.
I'll take it all!
Give me back, Yuta!
I refuse to let you kill
your best friend twice.
You